

Profile

Two years of experience as a software engineer in the full development life cycle and four years as a game software tester. Able to effectively selfmanage, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team. Seeking a role where I can apply my skills and meaningfully contribute to the organization while growing professionally.

Employment History

SDET II (Software Development Engineer in Test)

Experis Game Solutions

August 2022 – December 2022

Tempe, AZ

Worked as a developer in test for Age of Empires 4.

- Created a tool to simulate combat scenarios to produce game balance data
- Fixed and added functionality to a game-play bot automation tool

Test Associate III

Experis Game Solutions

November 2018 to July 2022

Tempe, AZ

Worked as a tester for The Master Chief Collection.

- Coordinated with the team to execute test plans and other self-directed testing
- Wrote bugs in Azure DevOps and verified fixes
- Wrote task reports summarizing test coverage and results
- Trained new members assigned to the same team on project processes and standards

Software Engineer II

General Dynamics Mission Systems

August 2014 to October 2016

Scottsdale, AZ

Worked on maintaining network and logging software for a satellite 3G network.

- Implemented fixes, unit tested, reviewed code, and wrote test plans for test team verification of fixed bugs
- Revised version description and installation documentation and created an installer for a subsystem used at site
- Maintained and created new tools to parse and correlate data in logs received daily from site to detect issues and monitor system health
- Evaluated and assisted with investigations for issues found by the test team

Education

B.S. Computer Science

Arizona State University

May 2014 - 3.83 GPA

Tempe, AZ

The Web Developer Bootcamp

Introduction to Databases

www.udemy.com

2019

www.coursera.org

April 2023

A course by Meta

Details

Phoenix, Arizona
623-498-9313
JaronLifsey@gmail.com
Portfolio

Skills

C++
C#
Java
OOP Principles
Software Testing
HTML, CSS, Type Script
HTML, CSS, Type Script GIT
HTML, CSS, Type Script GIT Agile
GIT

Soft Skills

Self-Directed

Communication

Critical Thinking